{
    "subject": "resource/Mike_Wallace",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Wallace, Myron Leon",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Mike Wallace is Wallace, Myron Leon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9403225183486938,
            "question": "What is the full name of Mike Wallace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8605644702911377,
            "question": "What profession might someone with the name 'Wallace, Myron Leon' have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8279613256454468,
            "question": "What is the last name of Mike Wallace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7859891057014465,
            "question": "What is Mike Wallace's middle name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7821189165115356,
            "question": "Does Mike Wallace go by his full name professionally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7464327216148376,
            "question": "What is Mike Wallace's first name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6939337253570557,
            "question": "How many names does Mike Wallace have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6815128326416016,
            "question": "Could Mike Wallace's middle name be a nickname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4118397831916809,
            "question": "Are there any famous people named 'Leon'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3791508972644806,
            "question": "Is 'Myron' a common middle name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Mike Wallace is Wallace, Myron Leon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7673_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people named 'Leon'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7673_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could Mike Wallace's middle name be a nickname?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7673_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many names does Mike Wallace have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7673_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7673_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7673_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7673_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7673_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7673_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7673_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7673_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7673_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7673_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7673_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is justified because all documents mention that \"Myron Leon 'Mike' Wallace\" was an American journalist, game show host, actor, and media personality. There are no contradictions in this information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided documents, Mike Wallace's full name is \"Myron Leon Wallace,\" not \"Wallace, Myron Leon.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provides his full name as Myron Leon Wallace, not Wallace, Myron Leon.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}